welcome to category five technology TV
カテゴリ5技術テレビへようこそ
episode 514 for Wednesday July 26 2017
2017年7月26日水曜日のエピソード514
I'm Jeff Weston I'm taking over the
私はジェフ・ ウェストン です。
hosting duties tonight Robbie's not here
任務をホスティング今夜 ロビーは ここにはありません
and with me is Sasha Sasha what is
私と一緒にSasha Sashaは何ですか？
coming up in the newsroom here's what's
ここでは何だ ニュース編集室 に来ます
coming up in the category five TV
カテゴリ 5のテレビに登場する
newsroom the world's first autonomous
ニュースルーム世界初の自律型
transport ship plans to set on suede
輸送船がスエードに乗る計画
onyx wages next year
来年のオニキス給与
a Swedish rail firm has approved
スウェーデンの鉄道会社が承認した
training m'q train phase as the name of
トレーニングのm'q 列車の フェーズの 名前として
their train follows an online poll
彼らの列車はオンライン投票に従う
Google is unleashing 20 million
Googleは2000万を解き放つ
lab-created
ラボ作成
sterile male mosquitoes on a city and
市の 滅菌オスの蚊
says it's a good thing and will help
それは良いことだと助けになる
control the mosquito population
蚊集団を制御する
according to the Federation against
反対連盟 によると
copyright theft British magazine Cody is
著作権盗難 英国雑誌Cody is
directing readers to copyright
読者に著作権を与える
infringing software and updated your own
ソフトウェアを侵害して自分自身を更新した
regulations in Canada make it legal to
カナダの規制は、
fly again stick around the full details
完全な詳細の周りに 再び飛んで飛ぶ
are coming up later in the show
ショーの 後半に登場 する
this is category five technology TV wild
これはカテゴリ 5の技術テレビ野生です
live recordings are trusted only to
ライブ録音だけ に 、信頼されています
solid-state drives by Kingston
キングストンによるソリッドステートドライブ
Technology revive your computer with
テクノロジーで コンピュータを 復活させる
improved performance and reliability
パフォーマンスと 信頼性の向上
over traditional hard drives with
従来のハードドライブ を
Kingston SSDs category 5 TV streams live
キングストンSSD カテゴリ5テレビストリームライブ
with Telestream Wirecast and nimble
Telestream Wirecastと迅速な対応
streamer tune in live every week on roku
毎週 ロク にライブストリーマーチューン
cody and other HLS video players for
コーディと他のHLSビデオプレーヤー用
local show times category 5 TV category
ローカルショータイムカテゴリー5テレビカテゴリー
5 TV is a member of the tech podcast
5テレビは技術ポッドキャストのメンバーです
network if it's tech it's here cat 5 TV
もしそれがここにいるのなら、それは技術だね。cat 5 TV
slash TPN and the international
スラッシュTPNと国際
association of internet broadcasters cat
インターネット放送局の 猫
5 TV slash ia IB
5テレビスラッシュ IB
I'm your host Jeff lesson and in the co
私はあなたのホストジェフレッスンで、 共同で
seat tonight
今夜席
taxidermy de though you're probably
剥製デ あなたは おそらく しているものの
wondering where's rowdy he's actually
彼が実際に どこにいるのか不思議です
taken the night off this is the first
これをオフにして撮影したのは最初です
time Robby's had a night off in the show
時間のロビーのショーで夜を過ごした
since its creation true there was the
真の創造以来、
one time he like tried to let go of the
彼が好きな1時間が手放すことを試みました
reins and he sat in the audience and
彼は 聴衆 に座り、
actually a lot higher so much yeah
実際に はるかに高いのでそんなにええ
hopefully we don't burn the place down
うまくいけば、我々はダウン の場所を焼却しないでください
we'll see how it goes but he did give
私たちはそれがどのように行くのか見るでしょうが 、彼は与えました
some really good instructions and when
いくつかの 本当に良い指示といつ
in doubt he is available if something
疑問が ある場合 は 、何か
goes wrong so if I randomly just pick up
私がランダムにちょうど拾うなら間違ってしまう
my cell phone I'm like you know that
私の携帯電話私はあなたがそれを知っているようだ
I've screwed up I truly do want to prove
私は私が 本当に 証明 し たいん 台無しにしました
that we like don't need him we need him
私たちが 好きなのは彼を必要としない
but like today we won't need him so that
今日のように彼を必要としないように
means that I'll be really counting in
私 が本当に数えていることを意味する
the chat remember things go awry to hell
チャットは 地獄 にうんざり する ことを覚えている
me and so one of the things with Robbie
私とRobbieのものの一つ
not being here is I realized that I am
ここにいない私は私が気付いている
way more dependent on his tech knowledge
彼の技術知識に依存する方法
that I realized I never had any doubt
私は決して疑いを感じなかった
how dependent on his technology
彼の技術にどのように依存する
yeah well I'm spending there he's like
ええ、うん、私は彼 がそこ にいるのを好む
also what are you going to cover for the
また、あなたは何のためにカバーするつもりですか？
show I'm like what do I know for tech do
私はテクノロジーのために何を知っているのか
I know what my idea was what my small
私の 考えは私のもの
idea was like maybe I could bring in my
アイデアは、 多分私は 私の中に 持って来る ことができるようなものでした
switch because I just like it got in
私はちょうどそれが 入って いるので、スイッチ
rollers oh sure yeah I know what you
ローラーああ 確かに私は あなた が何を知って いる
spend in everything I am okay with an
私は 大丈夫 だ すべてのものに 費やします
hour of playing video games that would
ビデオゲーム をする時間は
be fun uh-huh well next time next time
次回は楽しみにしてね
Robbie has a day off I do have an idea
ロビーには休み があります。アイデアがあります。
for the future and I think we've talked
将来の ために 私 たちは話したと思う
about it on a previous episode but I
それについては、以前のエピソード が、私 に
want to build a full-blown arcade system
本格的なアーケードシステムを構築したい
with a Raspberry Pi right so that will
それでラズベリーパイと一緒に
be coming sometime in the future before
将来的に 前に来ること
I die I hope but that's going to be one
私は死ぬと思うが、それは1つになるだろう
of those shows where it takes a lot of
それが がかかる ものを 示しているの
prep work because I'm going to have to
私はしなければならないので、準備作業
actually build the frame and all that
実際 にフレームを 構築 して
kind of stuff and you know so it'll be a
何かのものと あなたは知っているので、それは
lot of woodworking not so techie but
木工の多くは そうではない が、
it'll still be fun it'll be amazing
それはまだ 楽しいだろうそれは 素晴らしい だろう
mm-hmm but for tonight's show we're not
MM-うーんしかし、今夜のショーのために私たちでは ありません
really showing you tech we're going to
本当に私たちに行くテクノロジーを示しています
tell you about tech that's right
技術について正しいことを教えてください
tons of news about tech yes now not tech
テクノロジーに関するニュースのトン
but related to physics and engineering
物理学と工学に関連する
and repairs and stuff how was your bike
あなたの自転車はどうだった？
ride home last week oh okay so last week
先週先週家に帰ったよ
I told you about how I got stuck in the
私は私が で 立ち往生し てしまったかについてあなたに言いました
worst storm ever two weeks ago yes so I
2週間前の最悪の嵐
was all eager because the four
すべてが熱望していたのは、4人
Cass was blissfully amazing last week so
先週はキャスがすっごく驚いていた
I was like I'll just ride home joyously
私はちょうど家に愉快に乗るようなものだった
not that I had any other option at all
私は他の選択肢も全く持っていなかった
because I don't have a car so I served
私は 車を 持っていない ので 、私は 役立ちました
biking along happy as can be going well
幸せに自転車で 行く ことができますよう に
and then my chain broke not only my cane
私の鎖は私の杖だけでなく
my derailleur snapped in half I didn't
私のディレイラは半分にスナップした
even know that could happen I am really
それが起こる可能性があること を私が本当に知っている
it's the thing that moves your chain
それはあなたのチェーンを動かすものです
from like also whatever the guy really
同じように、その男が本当に何でも
cares it's a ring that moves the gears
ギアを動かすリングだよ
to the different spots so you were stuck
あなた が立ち往生した ので、別の場所に
in one gear then no my chain also broke
1つのギアで私のチェーンも壊れていない
in half well yeah so both went so the
半分でええ、そう両方は行ったので
derailleur snapped it broke my chain
ディレイラーが私の鎖を壊した
okay so I was in the middle of not
大丈夫だったので、私は中にいませんでした
everybody hears from Barry or familiar
誰もがバリーやおなじみから聞いた
but I was in Wellington and Bayfield up
私はウェリントンとベイフィールドにい た
right in the middle of the intersection
交差点 の 真ん中で右
so I'm picking up parts of my bike in
私は 自転車の 一部をピックアップしています
the middle and yeah it was awesome Pete
中央とええ それは 素晴らしい ピートだった
while people were just that people are
人々は、 人々がいる だけのことでした
good people are good there's good people
良い人は 良い人があると 良いです
okay so on Wednesday evenings in Barry
バリーの水曜日の夕方に 大丈夫です
they have I guess they call it I don't
彼らは私は彼らが私はそれを呼び出すと思います
know what it's called even but they have
それが何であるかを知っているが、彼らは持っている
movies in the park of Annette's point
アネットの点の公園の映画
which is like they for me her favorite
それは彼女の好きな 私の ための彼らのよう なものです
thing
もの
Hirano reason tonight is the life of
ヒラノ理由今夜 は
pets anyway oh right it's Wednesday
ペットとにかくオハイオ州それは水曜日です
night okay so I'll be fine I was really
夜は大丈夫ので 、 私は 本当に 大丈夫 でした
lucky this really sweet guy and I really
この本当に甘い男と私は本当に幸運な
I should have told him where I was
私はどこにいたのか教えてくれたはずです
coming from so that he could watch the
そこから来て、彼は
show this really sweet guy named Peter
ピーターという名前のこの本当に甘い 人を見せて
his name was Peter I think it was like
彼の名前はピーターだった
this is not a great place to be stuck
これは立ち往生するのに最適な場所ではありません
wait with you and you get picked up my
あなたと一緒に待って、あなたは私の拾いに来る
other friend Mel came and picked me up
他の友人のメルが来て、 私を拾った
but it was it was an ordeal and Dave the
しかし、それは試練であり、 Dave the
next day when I would be fixed my bike
私の自転車を修理する翌日
because exactly how smart I am with tech
私がハイテク に いかにスマートなのか
with Robbie is how smart I am with bikes
ロビーと一緒に私 は自転車に いかに賢いですか？
with Dave so he fixed my bike completely
Daveと一緒に彼は私の自転車を完全に固定 しました
okay so today it's going to be the
大丈夫そう、今日は 可能になるだろう
perfect ride home good times
完璧な帰宅の良い時
well seeing is this is all about you
よく見ているのはこれが あなたの すべて です
right about now what's going on in the
今のところ 、
news room let me check here are the
ニュースルームは私がここにチェックさせて
stories were covering this week in the
物語は今週
category 5 TV newsroom
カテゴリ5 TVニュースルーム
the world's first autonomous transport
世界初の自律輸送
ship plans to set out on its voyages
船の航海計画
next year
来年
a Swedish rail firm has approved
スウェーデンの鉄道会社が承認した
training m'q train pace as the name of
トレーニングのm'q 列車のペースの名前 として
their train following an online poll
オンライン投票後の列車
Google is unleashing 20 million
Googleは2000万を解き放つ
lab-created seral male mosquitoes on a
研究室で作成されたSeralオスの蚊
city and says this is a good thing and
これ は良いことだと
will help control the mosquito
蚊を制御するのに役立ちます
population according to the Federation
連盟 に よると 、人口
against copyright tasks British magazine
イギリスの雑誌
Cody is directing readers to cop to
コーディーは読者を警官に導いている
copyright infringing software and
著作権侵害ソフトウェア
updated drone regulations in Canada make
カナダの更新ドローン規制 作ります
it legal to fly again these stories are
これらの物語を再び飛ばすことは合法です
coming right up don't go anywhere
どこにも行かないで右に来る
Jeff Westen Gemma you're building a
ジェフ ウェスティンジェマ あなたが構築している
brand-new beautiful website what are you
あなたは何ですか？
alright you're terrible actor
あなたはひどい俳優です
what does where acting comes into play
何が演技になるのか
oh I don't know what are thing you're
ああ私は あなたがしている もの が何であるかを知りません
supposed to act ok fair enough
十分に大丈夫だと思われる
underling a really cool website are you
本当にクールなウェブサイトを下っ端あなたをしています
building a really cool website you need
あなたが必要とする本当にクールなウェブサイトを構築する
hosting one of the things about a
物事の 1つ をホスティングする
hosting account is you don't want to
アカウントをホストすることはしたくないですか？
have limitations put on your website
あなたのウェブサイトには制限があります
it's sure how much hard drive space you
どのくらいのハードドライブスペースを
have how many email account how many
メールアカウントの数
domains can point to it well we've got
ドメインはそれを うまく 指し示すことができます
an amazing deal for you for a very
非常にあなたのための素晴らしい取引
limited time cap 5 dot TV slash dream
制限時間キャップ 5ドット TV スラッシュドリーム
host for just $5 and a bit of change per
ちょうど5ドルでホストし、 1回あたりの変更
month you are going to get unlimited web
あなたは無制限のWebを取得 しようと している月
site hosting unlimited email accounts on
無制限の電子メールアカウントをホストするサイト
that hosting service you are also going
あなたが行っているホスティングサービス
to receive a free domain name the roots
無料のドメイン 名に ルーツを 受信します
are your own com dice to put that
それを置くあなた自身のCOMサイコロです
amazing website that you've been working
あなたが働いていたすばらしいウェブサイト
on on there if you run if you want to
あなたがしたい場合は実行するとそこに
build a wordpress site fine
WordPressのサイトを 細かく構築する
sign up cat5 dot TV slash DreamHost
サインアップ cat5 dot TVスラッシュDreamHost
still fulfill of a paper something just
まだ紙の何かを達成する
don't do it but hey it's a great deal
それをしないでくださいねえ、それは大したことだ
folks best deal you're going to find
あなたが見つけようとしている人には最高の
five dollars and change per month put a
毎月 5ドルと1 ヶ月に
cap five dot TV slash dream host
キャップ5 ドットテレビスラッシュドリームホスト
I'm Sasha tomatoes in here the top
私はここの サシャのトマトです
stories for the week of July 26 2017 a
2017年7月26日の週の話
foolish ship to be christened the Yarra
ヤラ に 洗礼を受けた 愚かな船
berkland is expected to start sailing in
berklandは でセーリングを 開始すると予想されます
initially delivering fertilizer along 30
最初に肥料を30
a 37 mile route in southern Norway the
ノルウェー南部37マイルのルート
electric powered ship will be miniscule
電動の船は極小です
by modern standards with the capacity
能力を 備え た現代の基準によって
for 100 to 150 containers but its
100〜150の容器では
arrival could be a huge turning point
到着は大きな変わり目になる可能性があります
for the global shipping industry the
世界の海運業界にとって、
ship according to The Wall Street
ウォールストリートに 沿っ て出荷
Journal will cost twenty five million
ジャーナルは2,500万
dollars about three times as much as a
約3倍を ドル
conventional ship of similar size but
類似のサイズの従来の船
will save up to 90% in annual operating
年間稼働率を最大90％削減
costs by eliminating both fuel and crew
燃料と乗組員の両方を排除することによるコスト
though it's project is it though it is
それは プロジェクト だけど
projected to launch next year it will
それは来年起動 すると予測
transition to fully autonomous
完全に自律的に移行する
operations only in stages it will first
最初の
be operated by an onboard crew then
次に乗組員が操作する
remotely before becoming fully self
完全に自己になる前に遠隔から
guided by 2020 that is around the time
2020年までに案内されています
rules governing autonomous ships are
自律船を支配する規則は
expected to be in place okay so Jeff how
Jeffの やり方は 大丈夫だと思う
you feel about that aye I think it's a
あなたはそれ について 感じます
very cool idea what to see is not a
参照するにはどのような非常にクールなアイデアではありません
place to be playing around with a fully
周りを完全に 遊ぶ場所
automated boat I mean like is it going
私が好きなわけ自動化されたボートは、 それが 起こっ ています
to be able to adapt to things like hey a
A ちょっとのような ものに適応できるようにするには
hurricane just showed up in the middle
ハリケーンがちょうど中間に現れた
of the ocean okay so here's the thing I
ので、ここで大丈夫 海 の 事です I
feel like it because it's safer for
それがより安全な ので、 それの ように感じる
people to not be on the ship in the
船に乗らない人
hurricane I'm ok with the ship
ハリケーン私は 船で大丈夫 です
perhaps.perhaps full of fertilizer going
おそらく、おそらく 肥料がいっぱいいっぱいです
down but I feel like it's better for the
しかし、私は それがより良いのよう に感じる
people to not be on board if there's
そこにいる人はいない
going to be a catastrophic failure of
の 致命的な障害 になるだろう
some sort not that I think that the
いくつかの並べ替えていない私はと思うこと
ocean needs 150 containers full of
海は150の容器がいっぱい必要です
fertilizer well that's just a crisis I'm
肥料はそれ だけの危機だ
sure that's a bad yeah I'm ever waiting
確かにそれは悪い私はこれまで待っている
to use it no I think it's very cool
私はそれが非常にクールだと思うそれを使用する
though but I just I can't
しかし私は ちょうど私はできません
wonder like is the a I can be ready for
私は準備ができているようなのだろうか？
the elements I mean we've got autonomous
要素私は自律性を持っていることを意味する
cars that can't pick up or certain
ピックアップできない、 または確実でない車
autonomous cars but self-driving cars
自律車、しかし自走車
that can't pick up jumping kangaroos in
カンガルーを 拾うことができない
Australia but now I'm going to send a
オーストラリア、しかし今私は
ship out into the water like is it going
それが行くように水中に船を出す
to be programmed for icebergs is it
氷山の ためにプログラムされること はそれです
gonna be programmed for other we're all
私たちはすべて他人のためにプログラムされるつもり
really good with the icebergs Jeff well
よく氷山ジェフと本当に良いです
there was one vote that struggled with
1つの投票で苦労した
the iceberg or a iceberg what yeah oh I
氷山や氷山何 そうそう I
like they're doing in stages right so
彼らは すぐにそうしているように
it's kind of like the the new story that
新しい話のようなもの です
we had last week
私たちは先週
with the race cars where there was a
あったレースカー で
human in the car that would guide right
右に導く車の中の人間
yes so it's similar to that in that
はいそれはそれ でそれ に似ています
people will be in the boat and train the
人々はボートに乗って
boat probably the route and it likely
ボートおそらくルートとそれはおそらく
won't deviate from that right so now the
その権利から逸脱することはありませんので、今すぐ
thing the thing is I mean if I were to
物事は、 もし私が
take kind of a nother side of it yeah
ええ、それのNotherの側 の種類を取ります
now people are out of jobs right there's
今、人々は すぐ に 就職してい ない
I would making that argument for a year
私はその議論を1年間続けようと思います
I know some your writing on this one but
私は この1つ上の いくつかのあなたの書き込みを知っている が、
people are perhaps now available to get
人々 はおそらく 今入手可能です
safer on shore jobs than on the sea
沿岸部の仕事で海よりも安全
that's true that is true
それは事実です
those disappointed when Britain rejected
イギリスが拒否したときに失望した人
the name bode mcboatface for a polar
極のための名前bode mcboatface
research ship should find joy in the
研究船は、
name of a new train in Sweden after a
スウェーデンの新しい列車の名前
public vote a Swedish rail operator has
スウェーデンの鉄道オペレーターが持っている公の投票
vowed to name one of its trains train
列車の列車の名前を列挙することを誓った
emic train face The Guardian reports a
エミック列車の顔ガーディアンは、
training act train face 149 percent of
トレーニングの 列車の 顔 149 パーセントの
the votes in the name and competition
名前と競争の中で投票
conducted by online train operator MTR
オンライン列車の運転MTR が実施
Express in Swedish newspaper Metro
スウェーデンの新聞メトロで急行
beating choices such as McCann Miriam
McCann Miriamのような選択肢を打つ
and Poseidon the train will run between
ポセイドンとの 間で 列車が 走る
the Swedish capital Stockholm and
スウェーデンの首都ストックホルムと
Gothenburg the country's second biggest
国の二番目に大きいイェーテボリ
city and here said another train had
ここには別の列車があった
been voted had been voted to be named
議決され て投票 された
Glenn an apparent tribute to an IFK
グレンは IFKへ の 明らかな賛辞
Gothenburg soccer team of the 1980s that
イェーテボリの1980年代のサッカーチーム
featured four players
4人の特集
of that name uncommon in Sweden
スウェーデンでは珍しいその名前の
including Glenn - who later captained
グレンを含む- 後にキャプテン
Liverpool okay so first thing I thought
リバプール 大丈夫だから 私が思った 最初の こと
is Glenn was a probably a nod to walking
グレンはおそらく歩くことにうなずいた
dead and I was completely wrong
死んで私は完全に間違っていた
but what would you name it train after
しかし、 あなたはそれを後で訓練しますか？
character from The Walking Dead I don't
私はしないで 歩く死からの キャラクター
know that's the only Glenn I know I
それが 私が知って いる 唯一の グレンだと知っている
guess then training me train face I'm so
私は そう私は 顔を養成訓練、その後推測
happy that there aren't public polls for
世論調査がないことを幸せに
naming children there are there better
子供に名前を付けてそこに良い
not be well I don't know about public
うまくない 私は 一般公開 について知らない
polls but I know I've seen people where
世論調査だが、私は人々を見たことが分かっている
they've done fundraisers online like hey
彼らはねえのようにオンラインで募金活動をしてきた
name our baby and for every vote it's
私たちの赤ちゃんに名前をつけて、すべての投票のために
like 5 bucks and baby McBay BJ's know
5ドルのように、赤ちゃんのマクベイBJは 知っている
there's been some wild ones II yeah and
いくつかの野生のものがありました。
I don't know if it's ever actually been
私はそれが実際にされているかどうかわからない
tested legally in court my thought is if
法廷で法的にテストされた私の考えは
you're going to take money and somebody
あなたはお金と誰かを取るつもりです
wins you have to name their kid that I
あなたは 私のことを 子供に命名する必要があります
don't I love the name train emic train
私は列車の名前を愛していないemic列車
case to be honest with you I don't love
私は愛していないあなたに正直である場合
the name Poseidon for a train if that
もしそれが列車の名前ポセイドン
seems weird and I'm deciding like a
奇妙に思えて、私は
water you think yeah yes okay so I would
あなた はそう 大丈夫だと私は 思います
have expected just people to be voting
人々だけが投票すること を期待 している
for like Thomas the Tank Engine yeah how
トーマスのようなタンクエンジンのための方法
come he was in do Thomas but I don't
彼は トーマスにいたんだけど、私はしない
know maybe Thomas wasn't as riveting as
おそらくトーマスは
Glenn or trainee mix train face training
グレンまたは トレーニングのミックストレインの顔のトレーニング
my train base this is what our world is
私の列車のベース これは私たちの 世界です
they should have named the Train boaty
彼らはボートをボートに命名すべきだった
mcboatface that would have been a kick
キックされた mcboatface
in the teeth of the boat company yeah
ボート会社の歯の中でええ
well then Google's health care arm
よく、 Googleのヘルスケア部門
verily announced just before the weekend
真に週末の前に発表された
it will release 20 million sterile male
それは2000万の滅菌男性をリリースする
mosquitoes into the wild in Fresno
フレズノで野生の 蚊
County California don't panic it's to
郡カリフォルニア州はそれを慌てることはありません
test fighting diseases like zika dengue
ジカデング熱のような戦闘病をテストする
and chikungunya I'm glad I do not have
チクングニャと私は持っていないのでうれしい
that disease the deepa project will be
その病気 はdeepaプロジェクトになります
the biggest US study to set free
無料の米国最大の研究
mosquitoes infected with wool bhatia a
ウール bhatia aに 感染した蚊
common reproductive parasite the idea is
共通の生殖寄生虫のアイデアは
that the infected mosquitoes will try to
感染した蚊が
mate with wild females but the eggs laid
野生の雌と交配するが、産卵する卵
will not hatch and the mosquito
孵化せず、蚊
population will decline over time
人口は時間とともに減少する
a million mosquitoes will be released
百万の蚊が解放される
over a twenty week period okay I love
大丈夫 20週間にわたって 、私は大好きです
this story because I am like a mosquito
私 は蚊のような ので、 この話
magnet right so I love the idea of
磁石の ように私 はアイデアが大好き
getting rid of mosquitoes that shocks me
私に衝撃を与える 蚊 を 取り除く
what what the something is magnetized to
何が何に磁化さ れ ているか
me I'm an attractive individual no it
私は魅力的な人ではない
shocks me that you would be okay with
あなたが大丈夫だろうと私に衝撃を与える
messing with things look it it's not
ものを混乱させることはそれを見ない
like the mosquitoes are being taken over
蚊が引き継がれている ように
by robots okay they're just being
ロボットでは大丈夫です
eradicated there like GMO mosquitoes now
GMOの蚊が好きになった
but they're non reproductive GMO okay
しかし、 それらは 非生殖GMOは 大丈夫 です
but what are mesquite excuse that'd be
しかし、メスキートの言い訳は何だろう
good for something and now to have like
何かのために良いと今 ように持っている
sharing ginger blood okay I under - I
私は下 大丈夫生姜の血を共有する-私は、
get it but don't they feed like I wish
それを得るが、 彼らは私が望むようにフィードしないでください
anymore don't they feed birds Oh if you
もはや彼らは鳥を食べ ない
bet yes bats eat mosquitoes okay and
はいバットは 大丈夫 蚊を食べ て、賭け
probably frogs eat mosquitoes - frogs a
おそらくカエルは蚊を食べる- カエルは
mosquito I have no clue anyway I love
とにかく 私は大好きです。
the idea of less mosquitoes I don't love
私が好きではない 蚊の少ないアイデア
the idea of modifying something to make
何かを変える 考え
less mosquitoes I don't love the idea
少ない蚊私は アイデアが 大好きで はない
when has modifying something outside of
外部のものを変更しているとき
the natural course of creation ever gone
自然の創造の道 がなくなった
bad for the human race when has
人類に悪い
modifying this is this is ridiculous
この変更はこれはばかげている
you're doing right now
あなたは 今 やって いる
I just impression it was like well what
私はちょうど それが 何のよう な ものだった と思う
happened to the other ways of
他の方法で起こった
controlling mosquito populations like
蚊の個体群を制御する
don't let it don't let there be standing
立っていないようにしないでください
water right or seeing the lakes we have
右の水か、私たちの湖を見て
around this area but it's always windy
このエリアの周りが 、それは 常に風が強い です
but but like it's a standing water
しかし、それは立っている水のように
situation is Kito's breed in standing
キトの姿勢は立っている
water don't let there be standing water
水は立っている水を放さないでください
no but if you don't want there to
いいえ、もしあなたがそこにいたくないなら
genetically modify uh mosquitoes I don't
私は蚊を遺伝的に改変する
want there to be Zika or chicky Ganga or
ジカや ニワトリの ガンガが欲しい
whatever it's called yeah I don't want
ええ、私 は欲しくない
dengue fever
デング熱
I don't want fair isle mosquitoes unless
私は公正な島の蚊が欲しいのではない
they to choose to sterilize
彼ら は殺菌する こと を選択する
Sal's not socialization I'm okay with no
サルは社会化ではない私は いいえで大丈夫だ
mosquitoes okay that one's got my vote
私の投票を持っている蚊
according to the Federation against
反対連盟によると
copyright theft British magazine Cody is
著作権盗難英国雑誌Cody is
directing readers to copyright
読者に著作権を与える
infringing software Cody is a free legal
侵害ソフトウェアCody は無料の法律です
media player for computers but software
コンピュータが、ソフトウェアの メディアプレーヤー
add-ons can make it possible to download
アドオンで ダウンロード できるようにする
pirated content the complete guide to
海賊版コンテンツの完全なガイド
cody magazine instructs readers on how
コーディー 雑誌は読者に
to download such add-ons dennis
そのようなアドオンをダウンロードするdennis
publishing has not yet responded to a
出版はまだ
BBC request for comment the magazine is
雑誌の コメント の ための BBCの要求
available at a number of retails
多数の 小売店 で利用可能
including WH Smiths Waterstones and
WH Smiths Waterstonesおよび
Amazon it was spotted on sale by a cyber
Amazon は、サイバーによって販売されていた
security researcher Kevin Bauman it
セキュリティ研究者 Kevin Bauman it
repeatedly warns readers of the dangers
読者に危険を繰り返し警告する
of accessing pirated content online but
オンライン海賊版コンテンツにアクセスするのが、
one article lists a series of software
ある記事は一連のソフトウェアをリストしています
packages alongside screenshots promoting
スクリーンショットと一緒にパッケージをプロモートする
free TV popular albums and world sport
無料テレビ人気のあるアルバムとワールドスポーツ
check before you stream and use them at
ストリーミングしてから使用 する前に確認してください
your own risk the guide says before
ガイドが前に言ったあなた自身のリスク
adding that readers should stay on the
読者がにとどまるべきであることを追加します
right side of the law two of the add-ons
法の右側2つの アドオン
listed in the article are a banned list
記事に記載されている禁止リスト
maintained by the Cody developers Nate
Codyの 開発者Nateによって維持されています
Betts in Cody's community and project
コーディーのコミュニティとプロジェクトの ベッツ
manager says we don't support piracy
マネージャーは海賊行為をサポートしていないと言います
add-ons and so we don't like the idea of
アドオンのように私たちはアイデアが好きではありません
someone selling a magazine encouraging
雑誌を売っている誰かが励ます
people to use them WH Smith declined the
人々 はそれらを使用するWHスミスは、
comment but it is understood that the
コメントはありますが、
newsagent has no plans to stop the sale
newsagentは 販売 を 停止する 計画はありません
of the magazine Transport Canada has
Transport Canadaが持っている雑誌の
issued an update in recent week or in
最近1週間または
recent weeks to its interim order
最近の数週間 からその中間オーダーまで
governing the use of unmanned aerial
無人航空機の使用を管理する
vehicles or UAVs which include consumer
消費者を含む 車両またはUAV
and professional drones the previous
プロのドローンは前の
order which went into effect on March
3月 に発効 した注文
16th imposed harsh restrictions on when
16日に厳しい制限が課された
and where Canadians could operate their
カナダ人が彼らの
drones effectively grounding their
ドローンは事実上
aircrafts in most populated areas of the
人口の最も多い地域の航空機
country the rule surprised many
国ルールは多くを驚かせた
including amateur drone enthusiasts
アマチュア無人機 好きを含む
professionals and industry players they
プロと業界のプレーヤー
also prompted a strong backlash from
また、
drone owners who signed online petitions
オンライン請願書に署名した無人機の所有者
wrote to the Minister of Transport as
交通大臣に次のように書いた。
well as their local MP MPs and joined
ローカル MP MPと同様に
and on
〜と
group called node created by Chinese
中国語で作成されたノードというグループ
drone company DJI for the purpose of
ドローン会社DJI の目的のため に
making their voices heard those efforts
彼らの声がその 努力を聞いた
were apparently successful the new rules
新しいルールが明らかに成功し た
adjust the filament ations imposed by
によって課されたフィラメントを調整する
the March announcement earlier in the
それ以前の3月の発表
month that the Canadian launch of its
月 のカナダの打ち上げ こと
new drone the DJI spark Adam Liz Berg
新しいドローンDJIはアダム・リズ・バーグ
DJI corporate communications director
DJIコーポレートコミュニケーションディレクター
for North America Express expressed
北米Expressのための表現
frustration with transport Canada's
交通機関の不満カナダの
rules noting that they do that they
彼らがそうすることを指摘する規則
would do nothing to prevent drone pilots
無人機のパイロットを防ぐために 何も しません
from flying recklessly if that's what
それが何であれば無謀に飛行することから
they were determined to do well they
彼らはうまくいくと決心した
penalized the overwhelming majority of
圧倒的多数の
drone pilots who fly safely I'm not sure
安全に飛ぶ無人機のパイロット私は分かりません
how I feel about this one I like it
私はこの 1つ についてどのように感じているか、私はそれが好き
because it just goes to show you that
それ だけで こと を示す ことを 行くので、
your voice can absolutely be heard right
あなたの声は絶対に聞こえ ます
this is people who really stood up
これは本当に立ち上がった人々です
against some super limiting regulations
いくつかの超制限規制
and they changed the laws really see
彼らは実際に見ている法律を変えた
speeding up I love I love that they said
私は愛するスピードアップ私 は彼らが言った ことが 大好き
that look this is this is wrong you
これ はこれが あなた が間違っている こと を見 て いる
don't understand what we need to do and
私たちが何をする必要があるのか​​理解していない
you're not going far enough you're not
あなたは十分 に 遠くに 行か ない
doing what we need you're going the
私たちは、あなたが 行っ ている必要なものをやって
wrong area and like that
間違った領域など
what I don't like is that drones are
私が好きで はないのは、無人機が
just taking off in the last couple years
ここ数年の間に離陸する
as something fun to do like the fact
事実のように何か楽しいものとして
that my kids have a little teeny drone
私の 子供たちは少し小さな 無人機を 持っている
like are they going to be roped into
彼らは
these rules in some way shape or form it
これらの規則は何らかの形で形作るかそれを形成する
depends on the weight of them I suppose
私が推測する彼らの体重に依存する
yeah I mean a teeny drone it's yeah you
ええ、私 はちょっとしたドローン を 意味しています。
know but if we get the point where you
知っているが、もしあなたが
start upgrading to something bigger and
何か大きなものへのアップグレードを開始し、
maybe we're not using it for commercial
多分私たちは商業用に それ を 使用していないでしょう
purposes but is this going to impact the
この 目的 は 、
ability of just having fun and I can't
ちょうど楽しみの能力と私はできません
have a wonder how is this going to
どのようにこれが起こっているのだろうか？
affect like some of our shows like the
ショーのようにいくつかの
drone zone yeah so yeah you know I wish
ドローンゾーンええええええええええええええ、 私はしたい
Henry was here for this to weigh in on
ヘンリーはこのために体重を計っていた
it because Henry that's true he would
それは ヘンリー だから 、彼は本当だろう
have some good thoughts yeah he would
彼には良い考えがある
know exactly even what those regulations
それらの規制が何であるかを正確に知る
are whereas I'm not quite sure I
私は確信していませんが、私は
understand that you can't fly drones
あなたが無人飛行をすることができないことを理解する
after like up to like certain secured
後のように一定の安全のように
areas that you can't be in a airport
あなたが 空港に いられない地域
sort of
一種の
scenario or a little Jersey stuff like
シナリオや小さなジャージーの ようなもの
that yeah but still I don't know what
ええ、でもまだ私は何を知りません
and I just I think maybe they're jumping
私はちょうど彼らがジャンプしているかもしれないと思う
the gun on some of the rules that
いくつかの規則の銃
Transport Canada is rolling out yeah I
カナダ移送はええええ
think is a drone really transport hmm
ドローンは本当にhmmを運ぶと思う
depends on asset owned by Amazon I guess
私が推測するAmazonが所有する資産に依存する
ha ha ha ha okay good point I'll give
ハッハッハハッハッハー良いポイントを私が与えるだろう
you the big thanks this week to the
あなたに 今週 の 大きな感謝
Albuquerque turkey Roy W Nash and our
アルバカーキ・トルコのRoy Wナッシュと私たち
community of viewers for submitting
送信する視聴者のコミュニティ
surveys tests this week thanks for
調査は今週に感謝を テスト
watching the category-five TV newsroom
カテゴリ5のTVニュースルームを見て
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
好きで購読 する ことを忘れないでください
all your tech news with a slight Linux
わずかな Linuxを 使ってあなたのすべての技術ニュース
bias and for more free content be sure
バイアスとより多くの無料コンテンツのために確かめてください
to check out our website from the
から当社のウェブサイトをチェックアウト します
category-five TV newsroom i'm sasha
カテゴリ5テレビニュースルーム私はサシャです
dramatis thanks so much Sasha so if
登場のおかげでそんなに サーシャ もしそうであれば
you're watching you may have realized
あなたはあなたが実現しているのを見ている
that we had news quite early in the show
私たちはショーのかなり初期のニュースを持っていた
I messed up the format I even have it
私 は それ も持って いる フォーマットを台無しにしました
written down right here but I mess it up
ここに 書かれ ている が、私は それ を 台無しにする
anyway see that's what happens when
とにかくそれが起こるのは、
Robbie leaves things just go hmm so
ロビーは物事をちょうどhmmにする
anyway what we were going to be doing
とにかく私たちがやっていること
tonight
今晩
before the news that we're now going to
私たちが今行っているニュースの前に
do after the news if things you need to
あなたが必要とする もの が あれば 、ニュースの後に する
know from the world of tech so it's not
技術 の 世界 から知っている のでそうではありません
just news but it's what are some of the
ちょうどニュースですが、それはいくつかの
other things that are happening in the
で 起こっている他のもの
world of tech that may not make it to
に それを作るかもしれないハイテクの世界
the news room because we have stories
ニュースルーム我々は物語を持っているので、
submitted all the time but we can only
すべての時間を提出したが、我々はできる
get so many on every week so what Sasha
毎週あまりにも多くを得るので サシャ
and I thought we'd do is just kind of
私は私たちがやっていると思っていた
fill you know what's happening around
あなたの周りに何が起こっているか知っている
the world that's right yeah
そうだね
one of them that most people should be
ほとんどの人がそうでなければならない
excited about is Adobe is officially
興奮しているのはAdobeです
killing flash by 2020 not even going to
2020年までにフラッシュを殺しても行かない
give a moment of silence because it's
それがある ので、沈黙の 瞬間 を 与える
just wonderful it has been a long time
ちょうど素晴らしいそれは長い時間されている
coming ever since html5 flash has been
html5のフラッシュが行われて以来ずっと来ています
useless
役に立たない
right what do some things use only flash
いくつかのもの はフラッシュだけを使うの ですか？
I feel like you're yes that's I've
私はあなたがそう だ と思う
websites that may have not updated
更新されていない可能性のあるウェブサイト
technology like I know you can you can
私はあなたができることを知っているような技術
go to some gaming sites where you just
あなただけのゲームサイトに行く
play flash based games they just haven't
彼らがし ていないフラッシュベースのゲームをプレイ
bothered to update to get with the times
時代に合わせて更新するのに気をつけた
and they're stuck back in something from
彼らは何から戻ってきた
the 1990s
1990年代
so but I mean like you've got Chrome
そうだけど、あなたは Chrome を持っているような気がする
Microsoft edge Safari they all stop
マイクロソフトのエッジ サファリ 彼らはすべて停止
blocking flash I think it was last year
私はそれが昨年だと思うブロックフラッシュ
you've got a couple of them that are
あなた はそれらのカップルを持っている
going to be doing some support into the
いくつかのサポートをしていること になるだろう
years ahead
数年前
like I think Microsoft edge is giving
私はマイクロソフトの エッジが与えていると思うように
some support in to 2019 something like
2019年のようなもののようなもの
that but as of 2020 Adobe you're saying
それは2020年のAdobeの言葉通りです
you know what enough is enough flash is
あなたは十分なフラッシュが十分であることを知っている
dead which is interesting because that's
それは面白いです
what Adobe really has been built on yeah
アドビが本当に構築したもの
so it's it's going to be neat to see
それはそれが見事 に なるだろう
them adapt and I know they've already
彼らは適応し、私は彼らが既に知っている
made steps with other areas but it's
他の分野と歩調を合わせたが、それは
kind of its kind of neat so flash is
そのよう なきちんとした種類 のフラッシュは
officially given the swan song I like it
正式に私はそれが好きな 白鳥の 歌を与えられた
yeah yeah right you have something about
ええ、そうです
cars right ok so the UK is banning the
車は OKですので英国 は禁止しています
sale of new gas and diesel cars starting
新型ガスおよびディーゼル車の販売開始
in 2040 and then by 2050 expected to
2040年には2050年までに
have none on the roads that's cool yeah
ええクールだ道路上のどれも持っていません
although it makes me feel a little bit
それは私が少し気分にさせる
of old because I retire in the 2040s so
私は2040年代に引退するので、古い
maybe I'll go to Europe and drive an
多分私はヨーロッパに行き、
electric vehicle I love it you know to
電気自動車 私はあなたが知っていることが大好き
be honest with you I've been watching
私が 見 てきたあなたと正直に
the Netflix documentary about that it's
それについてのNetflixのドキュメンタリー
called the pyramid code and I really I
ピラミッドコードと呼ばれ、私は本当に私です
don't
しない
it's a documentary about pyramids and
ピラミッドについてのドキュメンタリーです
how contrary to popular belief they were
彼らが一般的な信念に反する
actually used as I guess electrical
実際に私が推測する電気として使用される
conduit I don't know exactly but they
コンジット私は正確にはわからないが、彼らは
they created electricity it was like
彼らはそれは のようだった電気を作成しました
Tesla had the idea of electricity that
テスラは電気のアイディアを持っていた
wasn't made from combustion so I like
燃焼から作られたものではなかったので、私は好きです
the fact that we're going the route of
我々は の ルートを行っているという事実
green energy even though it seems like
それはのように見えても 、グリーンエネルギー
we're fairly delayed in it by 2040 we're
2040年までにはかなり遅れています
going to make it happen if that's
それが実現 すれば
stopping the sale so like you can't go
あなたが行くことができないように売りを止める
to Europe and buy a diesel vehicle
ヨーロッパに行き、ディーゼル車を購入する
perfect I mean that's really feasible
完璧な 私はそれが 本当に実現可能である ことを意味する
don't need to hear 20 years away yeah
20 年前に聴く必要はありません
there's no any except for the fact that
事実を除いて何もない
there is a transition period that needs
必要 移行期間が あり ます
to happen
発生する
it's not like we don't have the
私たちが持っていないようではない
technology now to make it happen we can
それは 私たちがすることができます 実現 するための技術になりました
totally be done with it now if we needed
私たちが必要であれば 、 今では 完全に完了して います
to we do need to I think it's kind of
私はそれは一種のだと思う と、私たち に 必要なのですか
cool I'm excited to see how it will be
私はそれがどのようになるか見て興奮している
rolled out some of the rules that come
来るルールのいくつかを出した
with it how it's going to change the
どのようにそれを 変更する つもりです
auto industry and how is it going to
自動車産業とはどのようになっていますか？
change the oil industry in Europe is a
ヨーロッパの石油産業を変える
big place
大きな場所
so if you're going to cut out the entire
あなたが全体を切り取るならば
sale and use of diesel and gasoline
ディーゼルとガソリンの 販売と使用
vehicles instead have a massive massive
代わりに車は大規模な大規模な
impact
影響
so let it be interesting very cool ok
とても面白いです よ
going from Europe to the US this one's
ヨーロッパから アメリカ に行く、この1の
kind of neat Girl Scouts of America
アメリカのきちんとしたガールスカウト
kudos to you so the Girl Scouts of
あなた への 誇り 、ガールスカウトの
America have decided to add 23 new
アメリカは23新しいを 追加することを決定しました
badges in the areas of science
科学分野のバッジ
technology engineering mathematics and
テクノロジー工学の数学と
outdoors so the science technology
屋外で科学技術
engineering math they call stem so
彼らは茎と呼ばれる工学的な数学
they're stem badges and outdoor badges
彼らは、 幹バッジや屋外のバッジ です
and of these 23 there's a robotics one
これらの23 の中にはロボット工学のものがあります
specifically for programming robotics
プログラミングロボット専用
keep your cool I know I'm like I want to
あなたのクールを保つ私は 私がしたい ようである こと を知っている
be a Girl Scout of America just so I can
アメリカのガールスカウトに なれる ように
get the badge the point is for the for
ポイントはのためのためのバッジを取得する
that one they have to create simple
彼らは単純に作成しなければならないこと
programs that would run a robot and
ロボットを走らせるプログラム
understand how the machine uses sensors
マシンがセンサーをどのように使用するかを理解する
ok so that's kind of cool on the
[OK]を ので、それは、 上の ようなクールです
engineering side of things they're going
彼らが行くものの工学的側面
to have to design a race car so design
レースカーをデザインする必要があるのでデザインする
the car design the track and carry out
車はトラックを設計して実行する
the test with fair rules so I guess that
公正なルールでテストしてみ てください
so that nobody loses and everybody gets
誰も敗北して誰もが得ることができないように
a medal I don't know what the fair rules
メダル私は公正なルールが何であるかわからない
means that's you know annihilating the
それを あなたが知っていることを意味する
other ones well see I like healthy
他の人は私が健康が好きだとよく分かる
competition but I just I think this is
競争が、私はちょうど これが
awesome
驚くばかり
the other one that they're rolling out
彼らが展開しているもう1つ
within that is with some of the
その中には、
programming they're working with other
彼らは 他の人 と一緒に働いて いる
companies from tech related groups like
ハイテク 関連のグループの企業
code
コード
org size starter Goldie box and this
orgyのスターター ゴールディボックス とこれ
goes with other badges that they're
他のバッジ と一緒に行く
going to be rolling out next year that
来年になる予定だ
they've already announced for website
彼らは既にウェブサイトのために発表した
designer and fiber security which is
デザイナーとファイバーセキュリティは
very cool not too many clubs teach kids
非常にクール ではない、あまりにも多くのクラブは、 子供たちを教えます
about cybersecurity so I think this is
サイバーセキュリティについてはこれ が
great but the interesting thing but why
偉大だが興味深いのはなぜ？
they're doing this is Girl Scouts of
彼らはガールスカウトの
America has found that almost that their
アメリカはそれがほとんど 自分のことを発見しました
members know if that's the word you call
メンバーは、それがあなたが呼ぶ 言葉かどうかを知っています
them they're almost twice as likely as
彼らは、
non Girl Scouts to participate in stem
非ガールスカウトが茎に参加する
and outdoor activities
アウトドアアクティビティ
sixty percent versus thirty five percent
60 ％対 35 ％
and as well Girl Scouts are more likely
ガールスカウトもそうだ
to get careers in STEM industries law
STEM業界の法律で就職する
and business nice that's very nice so
そしてビジネスはとても いいですね。
not only is it about getting a badge and
バッジを取得するだけでなく、
learning some really cool stuff but it's
本当にクールなものを学んでいますが、 それは
setting you up for the next phase in
次の段階 での ためにあなたを設定します
life which is your career other is often
他の あなたのキャリアである 人生 はしばしばです
what a great move I love it it's great
私はそれを愛する偉大な動きはそれは 素晴らしいこと です
well done Girl Scouts of America good
ガールスカウト、アメリカの良いスカウト
job all right what have you got okay so
仕事は大丈夫 です
here are this is quite the list of how
ここに これはかなりのリストです
our lives will change dramatically over
私たちの生活は劇的に変わるだろう
the next 20 years is this an op-ed like
次の20年はこれのような作品です
an opinion piece or is this like looking
意見募集やこれを見ている
at the transition of tack and where is
タックの移行時にどこに
it looking at the transition of tack
タック の移行 を 見る
okay alright so there's quite a few of
大丈夫 大丈夫そう の かなり の数が あります
these so we can drill through them it
これらを掘り下げることができ ます
looks like uber to do is just a software
uberのように見えるだけのソフトウェアです
tool so uber will be the biggest taxi
ツールのようにuberは最大のタクシーになります
company in the world really yeah
世界の企業は本当にええ
with all the challenges they're facing
彼らが直面している すべての 課題で
mm-hmm
mm-hmm
higher B&amp;B is now the biggest hotel
より高いB＆Bは現在最大のホテルです
company in the world yes do that yeah
世界の会社はいそうする
artificial intelligence computers become
人工知能コンピュータが
exponentially better in understanding
指数関数的に理解しやすい
the world this year computer beat the
今年の コンピュータ は世界を 打ち負かす
best goal player in the world ten years
世界10年ベストゴールプレーヤー
earlier than expected sorry the best
予想より早く申し訳ありませんが 最高です
what goal player go player I don't know
ゴールプレイヤーがプレイヤーを行く何私は 知りません
what that is I
私 は何ですか？
I don't know what go player is but you
私はプレイヤーが何であるかわからないが、あなたは
know it's interesting it was last week
先週だったのが面白いことを知っている
or the week before we had the composer
私たちが作曲家を迎える前の週
software that was run by AI so music
AIによって運営されていたソフトウェア
that's created by artificial
人工で作られた
intelligence
インテリジェンス
there was beautiful music it was really
それは本当に 美しい音楽 があった
quite moving so that's very cool now one
かなり動いているのでとてもクールです
of the things with AI is IBM's Watson
AIのものは IBMのワトソン
mm-hmm
mm-hmm
so you can get legal advice from Watson
ワトソン から法的助言を得ることができます
that's right they said that like 90% of
それは彼らの90％のような
all law jobs will be done you I guess
すべての法律の仕事は私が推測するあなたに 行われ ます
you can self represent when you have you
あなたはあなたがいるときに自分を表現することができます
know Watson behind you oh alright what
大丈夫 ああ 、あなたの後ろにワトソンを知っています
else's are coming up
他にも来ている
Watson help nurse diagnose cancer so no
ワトソンヘルプ看護師が いないので、 癌を診断します
that's right no yep yep so by 2030
それは右の 2030年までにそう 何 うんうんの ですん
computers will become more intelligent
コンピュータがよりインテリジェントになる
than humans in the medical industry I
医療業界の人間 、私は より
that's kind of scary
それは一種の恐ろしい
considering that there's a lot of
多く の
exploratory medical research so it makes
探検的な医学研究はそれを作る
you wonder if it'll be like diagnosing
それが 診断のようなもの かどうか疑問に思う
things or if it will be for removing
物事を取り除くかどうか
diseases from the face of the planet
惑星の顔からの病気
like hey I figured out how to cure
ねえ、私は治す方法を考え出したように
cancer mm-hmm that'd be kind of wild it
がんmm-hmmそれ は野生の よう な ものだろう
says here that kids now will never need
ここでは子供たちが今では
to get a license and never need to own a
ライセンスを取得し、
car because of autonomous cars and all
自律車 とすべての ために車
of the driving companies know that's
運転している会社 の
what it's really yeah see I uh no I
それは本当にええ、私は私が ない 参照してください
don't like that and the need for cars
それと車の必要性が好きではない
will decrease by 90 to 95 percent so I
90〜95％減少するので、私は
suppose that would be high speed trains
高速列車であると仮定します
that's for a situation training ik train
それは、 ik列車の 状況 訓練のためです
face I can see getting rid of cars I can
私 は車を取り除くことができますか？
see the not need for a license although
ただし ライセンスの必要はありませ参照
that makes me sad because I mean that's
それは私がそれを意味するので私を悲しくする
like a rite of passage when you can get
あなたが得ることができる通過の儀式のように
your license and look forward to that
あなたのライセンス を受け取り、それを楽しみにし ています
you there got behind the wheel was a
あなたはそこに車輪の後ろに あった
great day
素晴らしい日
I actually loved having a cart while I
私は実際に 私 ながらカートを持つ愛し
did I love not having a car now so I'm
私は 今車を持っていないのが大好きでした ので、 私は
kind of on board with the no car thing I
車のないもので私はボードの種類私は
couldn't live without a car it says last
最後に言う車 なしでは生きられない
year more solar energy was installed
年以上の太陽エネルギーが導入された
worldwide than fossil energy companies
化石エネルギー企業 よりも世界的に
are desperately trying to limit access
必死にアクセスを制限しようとしている
to the grid to prevent competition from
との競争を防ぐために 、グリッド へ
solar home installations but it won't
太陽の家のインストールが、それはしません
last
最終
technology will take care of that
技術がその世話をします
strategy interesting hmm
戦略面白いhmm
well I mean that's the way things are
よく私はそれは物事が ある 方法です意味します
going with renewable energy now one of
再生可能エネルギーと一緒に 行く
the things I notice on your list is
私があなたのリストに気づい ていることは
about 3d printing we've covered that a
3次元印刷については 、
few times on the show and we did have
ショーで数回、我々は持っていた
that one interview last year with 3d
昨年のインタビュー で3d
printing how it will rock your world I
それがあなたの世界を揺るがす方法を印刷する
think the book was called very cool
本は 非常にクール と呼ばれていたと思う
stuff but this was saying that 3d
ものが、これは言っていた3d
printers will go down from 18,000 to
プリンタは18,000から
$400 within 10 years well last week
先週の 10年間で 400ドル
there was a story on a 3d printed heart
3D印刷された心 の話がありました
yeah right yeah so 3d printing not only
ええ、 はい、そう、3d印刷だけでなく、
will be less expensive but already if
安いが、すでに
it's being used I know that you can 3d
それは使用されている 私はあなたができることを知っている3d
print a house which is crazy well can 3d
よくクレイジーな家を印刷することができます
print a heart it just it really just
心を印刷し、それだけで、それは本当に ただ
changes the way I guess will view making
私が推測する方法を変える
like manufacturing right because now
今のような製造権のように
you're going to make this thing and
あなたはこの事をするつもりだと
it'll manufacture in just one piece you
それはあなた だけの作品で製造されます
know organs and so yeah my mind is now
臓器を知っているので 、私の心は今です
like often left field because I'm
私はいつも左のフィールドのように
thinking okay we've got really good
本当に良い と思っている
artificial intelligence that can do
できる人工知能
better than humans in some cases and now
いくつかの場合 、人間よりも優れている
we can 3d print organs how soon before
私たちは3次元の印刷機関をどのくらい前にできますか
we have like data like animatronic real
私たちはアニマトロニックリアルのようなデータを持っています
life cyborg type 1 of that'll like we'll
サイボーグ1 の タイプ は私たちのようになります
have animatronic type animals within 20
20以内にアニマトロニクス型動物を有する
years
年
I bring your cat back yeah all right I
私は あなたの猫 を持っ て戻って ええ、すべて私は
mean if you were to go to a hospital
あなたが病院 に行くならば
let's say and instead of having to wait
待つのではなく、言いましょう
to be triaged and go through if you
審査され、
could just stand in a scanner and find
スキャナに立って見つけるだけで
out right away what's going on huh be
すぐに何が起こっているのか分から ない
seen by what was it pepper this yes
それは何だったのか見た
after the animatronic nurse thing yeah
アニマトロニックナースの事の後、ええ
hmm that's very cool okay last one this
うーん、それは 大丈夫最後の1つこれは 非常に クールです
one kind of seen the markings of this
1つの種類のこのマークを見た
start a couple years ago in Sweden but
スウェーデンで数年前に開始したが
in Wisconsin there's a vending machine
ウィスコンシン州には自動販売機があります
company hmm that has opened up for their
それは 彼らのために 開かれた会社
employees to be microchipped and it was
従業員はマイクロチップ化され 、 それは
voluntary process and of their 85
自主的なプロセスとその85
employees 50 of them said yeah chip me
従業員の 50人が 、私のチップを私に言った
so the microchip will allow them to buy
マイクロチップは彼ら が購入 できるよう にする
snacks log into computers and use the
スナックは コンピュータにログインし、
copy machine now this was done two three
コピー機は現在 、 これが 行わ れ てい た 2〜3
years ago I think from a Swedish company
何年も前に私 はスウェーデンの 会社
where their entire business is microchip
それらの事業全体がマイクロチップ
so you just kind of swipe your hand and
だからあなたはあなたの手を軽くたたいて
your business comes to life but that's
あなたのビジネスは生きていますが、それは
the deal seasons with this company it's
この会社との取引の季節は
called three square market and on August
3平方メートルと呼ばれ、8月に
1st they're having a chip party where
彼らはチップパーティーをしています 。
they're all gonna get chipped at the
彼らはすべての
same time right I I musta mind on this I
この 私 に気musta同じ時間右II
love it for the simplicity of you
あなたの単純さのために それを愛する
wouldn't need a code to go into a door
ドアに入るためのコードは必要ありません
you would already know if you had the
あなたはすでにあなた が
security clearances you could easily
簡単にできるセキュリティクリアランス
open a door somebody else couldn't I
他の誰かが私にできなかった扉を開ける
don't like the fact that probably a
たぶん
reader could easily be manufactured they
読者は容易に製造できる
could probably reprogram a chip already
既にチップを再プログラムすることができました
implanted in them only or like to go
彼らだけに植え付けられたり 、行きたい
into doors are not supposed to be in or
ドアが中であることを想定していないにか
perhaps to be able to use or get
おそらく、 使用したり、取得することができるようにします
anything from the vending machine but
自動販売機からのもの
not have the money actually come out of
実際 の 出てくる お金を持っていません
their account like I feel like I trust
私のよう な彼らのアカウントは私が 信頼する ように感じる
the hackers of this more than I trust
私が 信頼する 以上のこのハッカー
the creators of
クリエイターの
well and it's funny that you say that
まあそれはあなたが 言う ことは面白いです
because they're the Nevada State Senator
彼らはネバダ州議会議員ですから
Becky Harris back in February tried to
2月に 戻ってきた Becky Harris は
introduce legislation preventing
立法を防止する
employers from forcing this on now I
雇用主はこれを今から強制するから
mean in this case it was voluntary it
この場合、 それは自発的であった
was hey who wants to sign up but what
サインアップしたいが
senator Harris was saying is that it's
ハリス上院議員は、
possible to hack the information that's
その情報 を ハッキングできる
contained within the chips but I mean
チップ 内に 含ま れ ていますが、 私は意味する
it's if you haven't seen it it's about
それはあなたがそれを見ていない場合、それは程度だです
the size of a grain of rice and they
米の穀物 の 大きさ
insert it between the four finger and
4本の指と
the thumb so like right in here I don't
親指はここのように私はそうではない
I hear I mean it's a radio frequency
私はそれがラジオ周波数であることを聞く
that it works on you've got people that
それはあなたに働いている人がいる
are you know there's all these studies
これらのすべての研究があることを知っていますか？
about how cellphones and all I will give
携帯電話と私がすべて与える方法について
you cancer like hey let's take a chip
あなたは、がんのようなちょっとのチップを見てみましょう
that works off radio frequencies and
それは、無線周波数をオフに動作 し、
shove it into your body
それをあなたの体に押し込む
right like it does this become a WSIB
それは 、これは WSIBになる ん右のように
thing if they get cancer in the hand
彼らが手に癌を発症した場合の事
right not so fast
あまり速くない
well I guess not only that but I would
まあ、それだけではないと思うけど、私は
worry about creating some sort of weird
何か 奇妙な もの を 作る心配
like two-tier situation there's the chip
二層のような状況ではチップがあります
than the unchipped right
非 権利化された権利 よりも
but what yes yes they're like it's like
しかし、はいはい彼らはそれのようなものです
a black mirror thing again well and you
もう一度よく黒い鏡のこと
know it's it's funny because I've heard
私は聞いたのでそれが面白いことを知っている
about the chipping technology since the
以来、チッピング技術について
80s and it's now kind of coming into
80年代に入ると
fruition but the basics of it has never
結実だが、その基本は決してない
changed it's still the exact same ordeal
それはまだ まったく同じ試練です
that it's going to be this thing that
この 事 になるだろう という こと
runs our lives and I is this dangerous
私たちの人生を動かし、 私はこの危険です
territory here yeah I feel like it's
ここの領土はええ、私は それのよう に感じる
weird to chip like a human but my
人間のようにチップするのは変だけど、私の
passport I mean socials and my passport
パスポート私は社会と私のパスポートを意味する
has a chip in it really I got a ten year
本当に私は10年のチップを持っています
passport and the inside the the front
パスポートと内側の前面
cover of it there's a there's a chip oh
それのカバーは、 ああ 、チップがある
so I guess they scan the passport then
だから私は彼らがパスポートをスキャンすると思います
they open it and as long as the
彼らはそれを開いて、 限り
information that pops up on their screen
画面上にポップアップする情報
looks the same as what's there it's not
そこにあるものと同じように見える
a forged document so if they have AI had
彼らがAIを持っていれば 偽造された文書だ
information in me that could and then in
私の中にあることができる情報
me and
私と
on me that they could I could prove that
彼らが私にそれを証明できるか
I wasn't a terrorist I guess which is
私は ある と思いテロリストではなかったです
this going to open the new door of
これは新しいドアを開くつもりです
crimes like AI was slashed and they
AIのような犯罪は削減され、
stole my chip mm-hmm like I know I know
私が知っている知っているように 私のチップ MM-HMMを盗みました
I'm not a fan of this one very
私は非常にこの1つのファンではない
interesting technology what they're
彼らは何をしている興味深い技術
using for not a fan of this one right
この1つの右のファンではなく
well that pretty much brings us to the
よく、 私たちを
end of the show um do you want to hear
ショーの終わり聴きたいですか？
something funny that I saw in the news
私がニュースで見た 面白い何か
this morning yes there is a tick in
今朝は はい。
northern Canada you know what it's on TV
北部のカナダではテレビで何を知っている
see so I'm sure that this is completely
私は これ が完全であると 確信し ています
a true story you had to bring this up so
あなた が これを持っ ていなけれ ば なら ない 真実の話
there's a tick and not a Lyme disease
ダニがあり、ライム病ではない
tick it's called like The Lone Ranger or
それは孤独なレンジャーのように呼ばれるか、または
something excessive weird tech name and
過度の奇妙な技術名と
it's after bites you releases a protein
それはあなたがタンパク質を放出した後です。
into your blood that makes you allergic
あなたの血にアレルギーを起こす
to red meat yeah you shared this one
あなた はこれ を 共有 した赤い 肉のええに
with me this morning I hope I never see
今朝 私と一緒に私は見たことがないといい
this tick because I love my meat ticket
このチック私は私の肉の 切符が 大好き
hilarious when my wife was pregnant with
私の妻が妊娠していたとき陽気だった
our first son she knew she was pregnant
私たちの最初の息子 彼女は彼女が 妊娠していた
the day after because she couldn't stand
彼女が立つことができなかったので 翌日
the smell of meat like sent her running
彼女の走りを送ったような肉の臭い
for the washroom so we went completely
洗面所のために 私たちは完全に行った
vegetarian for four months was any worse
4ヶ月間菜食主義者が悪化した
four months of my life it was painful
私の人生の 4ヶ月は苦痛だった
and when you're new in your marriage and
あなたが結婚して新しい時に
you're still trying to figure each other
あなたはまだお互いを見ようとしている
out and I thought hey when I go to work
私は仕事に行くときにちょっと考えた
I'm just going to hit McDonald's got a
私はちょうどマクドナルドをヒットするつもりです
burger I'll be fine I grabbed it around
バーガー私は 周りに それをつかんで大丈夫です
like two o'clock lunch time I get let's
2 時の ランチタイムの ように 私はしましょう
smell it on you and yes okay so I would
あなたにそれを嗅ぐとはい、大丈夫です
like I would leave the house at 7:00 to
私は7時 まで に家を離れるように
go to work go out and buy whatever was I
外出して 何でも買う
wanted at the time I mean because it's
それはだ から、私の言い たかった 時点 で
the morning it's breakfast at that point
朝はその時点で 朝食 です
but I would eat the breakfast and for
私は朝食を食べ て しまう ため
lunch but she would still know like look
昼食を食べたが、 彼女はまだ見栄えが分かる
I guess smell on your breth I call about
私はあなたの 兄弟 に 匂いを 感じ ます
12 hours later okay yep it's horrible Oh
12時間後に 大丈夫 うん、それは恐ろしいああです
see now you're just making me upset
今あなたが 私を 怒ら せているのを見 て
Sasha so if you got if you got bit by
サシャ。 もしあなたが手に入れ たら、ちょっと手に入れて。
the stick though it wouldn't matter if
それは問題ではないがスティック
you liked it or didn't like it you just
あなたはそれを気に入っていた、またはそれを気に入らなかった
wouldn't be able to eat it I would lose
それを食べること が でき ないだろう 私は失うだろう
although this is a hilarious
これは 面白いですが
this is more like tax Toxoplasma this is
これは Tax Toxoplasmaのようなもの です
that photos
その写真
Toxoplasma the reason why pregnant women
トキソプラズマ理由は 、 妊娠中の 女性
can't change kitty litter because
ので、猫のトイレを変更することはできません
there's a parasite called Oh who causes
原因となるOhと呼ばれる寄生虫があります
toxoplasmosis so it's very dangerous to
トキソプラズマ症は非常に危険です
unbolt or unborn children but it's a
裸の子供や胎児はいない が、それは
it's a parasite that gets into your
それ は あなたの体 に入る 寄生虫 です
brain and it changes human behavior so
人間の 行動を 変える
it slows your reaction time so increases
それはあなたの反応時間を遅くします
the likelihood of a of a car accident it
車の事故の可能性も
also is proven to make men more
さらに男性を作ることが証明されている
aggressive and women more passive
積極的で女性よりパッシブ
so they actually there's a theory that
実際には、
it has shaped our culture that more
私たちの文化は、
people than we imagine have
私たちが想像する以上の人々
toxoplasmosis oh yeah oh not a random
トキソプラズマ症オハイオ州オハイオ州オー
parasite talk yeah I think that parasite
寄生虫の話ええ、私はその寄生虫
needs to go the way of the mosquito
蚊の道を行く必要がある
that's that's what I think that's right
それはそれは私が右だと思う何です
all right well up that's pretty much it
すべての権利だけでなくそれはかなり それ だアップ
for us a couple things to be aware of if
私たちのためにいくつかのこと を知っておく必要があります
you have not checked out our forums its
あなたは私たちの フォーラムを チェックアウトしていない
forum category 5 TV post a picture of
フォーラムカテゴリ 5のテレビの画像
yourself that's right so we did that
私たちが いることを やった ので、自分でそれは そう です
this week so we did do that this week so
今週はそうしました
you can check out that photo as well
あなたはその写真もチェック アウトすることができます
we've got our partners if you want to
あなたが望むなら私たちはパートナーを持っています
purchase something on Amazon use a
Amazonで購入するものは
partner links lots of people buying
パートナーリンク多くの人々が 購入
things like toiletries and household
トイレタリー や家庭の ような もの
products and you know it's being quite
あなたはそれがかなりあることを知っています
you know helpful for the show because
あなたはショーに役立つことを知っています
every time you purchase through Amazon
Amazonで購入するたびに
or any of our partner links the you know
またはパートナー のいずれかが、あなたが知っている リンク
we get a small cut that helps pay for
私たちは犠牲になる小さな切り札を手に入れます
our expenses so for everybody who's
誰もが私たちの費用
helping out thank you and check out shop
お手伝いをして店をチェックアウト
category 5 dot TV lots of good stuff
カテゴリ5 ドットテレビの良いもの
there raspberry pie you're awesome
そこに ラズベリーパイあなたは素晴らしいです
I love the pie alright so next week yeah
私は次の週のうん、そう 、パイを大好き
episode 515 you were not I are not here
エピソード515あなたは私がここにいない
I've taken over the news desk finally
私は最終的にニュースデスクを引き継いだ
get in that sucker back it's been a long
その吸盤に戻ってそれは長いされている
time and Shelley is going to be here and
時間とシェリーがここになるだろう と
we're going to be taking a look at a the
私たちは、 インクルード見てみる ことに なるだろう
ability to play video files from a USB
USBからビデオファイル を 再生する 機能
stick very very cool and I think this
非常に涼しい と私は これ を考える
might even help you with your upcoming
あなたの 今後の ことであなたを助けるかもしれません
wedding perfect so we could use all the
結婚式に最適なので、 私たちは すべての
help I can get ok that's my corporate
助けて もらえれば私の会社です
contribution to your wedding thank you
あなたの結婚式への貢献はありがとう
doing the show and
ショーをやって
so Robbie will be back next week we'll
ロビーは 来週 帰る 予定だ
have a normal format things won't be as
物事は普通ではない
messed up as they are right now but just
彼らは今のように混乱していますが、ちょうど
go cover it well Don go team dots
ドンは、 チームの ドットを 行っても 、それをカバーし て行きます
growing up there we go thanks so much
育って くれてありがとう
for watching and I will see you again
見て 、私は再びあなたに会います
next week
来週
that's what's good week
それは良い週だよ
[Music]
[音楽]